Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Cassettes, circa 1958-1999; 242 audiocassettes
  - Robertson, Kim, "Angels in Disguise", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0140)
  - Rooke, Fred, "Ballads of Bawlengro" (FSA 045), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0141)
  - Russell, Micho, "Under the Cliffs of Moher", 1990 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0142)
  - Sands, Colum, "The March Ditch", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0143)
  - Sands, Colum, "Unapproved Road", 1982 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0144)
  - Sands, Tommy, "Beyond the Shadows", 1992 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0145)
  - Sands, Tommy, "The Hedges of County Down and other Traditional Songs", 1989 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0146)
  - The Sean O'Neill Band, "50 Irish Party Songs", 1990, 1995 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0147)
  - Simmons, James, "The Rostrevor Sessions: Songs of Ulster", 1987 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0148)
  - Smith, Jesse, "The Hurricane", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0149)
  - Sorcha Dorcha, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0150)
  - Strachan, John, "Glenlogie" (FSA 065), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0151)
  - Strivender, Ed, "Yankee Come Home", 1990 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0152)
  - Sullivan, Tony, "Suly's Fancy", 1980 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0153)
  - Sullivan, William, "Traditional Irish Tunes", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0154)
  - The Temple House Ceili Band, "Music for Sets, Vol 1", 1991 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0155)
  - The Temple House Ceili Band, "Music for Sets, Vol 2", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0156)
  - U2, "The Joshua Tree", 1987 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0157)
  - Unknown, "An Talamh Breagha: A Collection of Gaelic Songs & Music from the Isle of Raasay", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0158)
  - Unknown, "At the Racket", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0159)
  - Unknown, "Cursa Gaeilge Leibheal", undated, 1981 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0160-031.001_0161)
  - Unknown, "Early Ballads in Ireland", 1968-1985 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0162)
  - Unknown, "Folkmusic & Dances of Ireland", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0163)
  - Unknown, "Hornpipes, Slip Jigs, Set Dances, etc...", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0164)
  - Unknown, "Jigs 1", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0165)
  - Unknown, "Last Night's Fun (Demo Tape)", 1999 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0166)
  - Unknown, "Mick Mulcahy agus Cairde", 1990 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0167)
  - Unknown, "Reels 1", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0168)
  - Unknown, "Reels 2", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0169)
  - Unknown, Side A: Thistle Accordion Band, "We Hate the IRA" Side B: "United We Stand", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0170)
  - Various Artists, "25 Years of the Kent State Folk Festival", 1992 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0171)
  - Various Artists, "All the Best: Folk Music of St. John's Newfoundland", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0172)
  - Various Artists, "And They Called It Ireland", 1993 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0173)
  - Various Artists, "Cardan's Favourite - Derek Bell, the Music of Cavalan Ud. II", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0174)
  - Various Artists, "The Celtic Klezmer Concert of the Second Millennium", 1995 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0175)
  - Various Artists, "Champions of Ireland Banjo", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0176)
  - Various Artists, "Come Back To Erin and Other Irish Love Songs", 1994 (Box 4, Audiocassette 031.001_0177)
  - Various Artists, "Dog Big and Dog Litte: Traditional Music and Song from the Counties Fermanagh and Leitrim", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0178)
  - Various Artists, "Flight of the Green Linnet", 1988 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0179)
  - Various Artists, "Fluters of Old Erin: Flute, Piccolo and Whistle recordings of the 1920's and 30's", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0180)
  - Various Artists, "Folk Music & the Lore of the Civil War", 1994 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0181)
  - Various Artists, "Guinness Live at the harp and thistle pub", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0182)
  - Various Artists, "The Mountain Road: The Traditional Music of Cork & Kerry", 1995 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0183)
  - Various Artists, "The Rights of Man: The Concert for Joseph Doherty", 1991 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0184)
  - Various Artists, "Stalker Wallace 1798-1998: Commemoration Album Covering 200 Years of Music, Song, & Verse" (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0185)
  - Various Artists, "Stark Raven", 1995 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0186)
  - Various Artists, "What's Your Name?: Rhymes and Rhythms from Pennsylvania's Neighborhoods", 1997 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0187)
  - Various Artists, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling, Volume 1", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0188)
  - Various Artists, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling, Volume 2", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0189)
  - Weavers, Donegal, "Last Day of the Northern Field: Memories of Pennsylvania's Coal Mines", 1992 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0190)
  - Whelan, John, "From the Heart", undated (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0191)
  - Wick, Regan, "Irish Piano and Stepdance", 1989 (Box 5, Audiocassette 031.001_0192)
  - Oversized Cassette Inserts & Booklets, 1989, 1991, 1995, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 28)
    James Morrison: The Professor (1989); Michael Coleman: 1891-1945 (1991); The Paddy O'Brien Tune Collection: A Personal Treasury of Irish jigs and reels (1995); Ed Reavy: The Collected Composition of Ed Reavy by Joseph M. Reavy (undated); Clare and Kelly: RTE Radio Traditional Music Archives (undated)